CHAKSHU DALUJA

UX/UI Designer, Melbourne, Victoria

A solution savvy designer with 10+ years of experience working and 1 year as a UX Designer/Product Owner in a fast-paced corporate environment.

Looking for an opportunity where I can bring together my vast work skills and newly acquired design proficiency, to deliver an enhanced digital user-centric experience.

KEY DESIGN PROJECTS

Tesla Model 3 | Introduced a New Feature

July 2022

Added a life-saving feature to the existing Tesla App. This feature assists paramedics and Tesla drivers during an accident.

Indigenous Literacy Foundation - NGO | Team Project

June 2022

Increased partnership engagement and enhanced user confidence by redesigning pages and information architecture.

Australian Tax Office (ATO) | Responsive website

May 2022

Redesigned and created a responsive website that enhanced the end-to-end user experience, leading to a greater use of digital taxation resources offered by the ATO and a reduction in the call volume.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX Designer/Product Owner | MOCS

One Year Project

- Develop a building app for desktop and mobile.
- Conducted **research**, established user needs and collaborated with application developers to achieve the desired outcome.
- Mapped a user journey to understand product touchpoints.
- Created **information architecture** leading to a streamlined user experience.
- Conducted user testing to validate requirements.
- · Aligned cross-functional stakeholders.

Owners Corporation Manager | MOCS

March 2021 - Ongoing

- Negotiated complex agreements to achieve win-win outcomes for all teams.
- Planned, coordinated, and prioritised major project works to rationalise delivery.
- Successfully handled pressures of delivering major projects work under various constraints, such as time, resources, etc.
- Established long-term partnerships with various stakeholders, resulting in increased confidence, trust and client satisfaction.

Executive Asset Assistant | Teska & Carson December 2019 – February 2021

- Served as a primary point of contact for all stakeholder on matters pertaining to directors, ensuring continuation of day-to-day operations.
- Prepared and delivered presentations, documents and reports for directors and other senior stakeholders.
- Applied critical thinking to manage and prioritise a broad variety of daily tasks.
- Facilitated workshops to brainstorm and achieve agreeable outcomes on complex matters.

Asset Manager | ANK Corp.

August 2018 - November 2019

- Researched and Identified opportunities to improve client's portfolio.
- Collaborated with managers to ensure effective implementation of business plan.
- Provided fit for purpose solutions to meet building compliance.

CONTACT

+61 433 271 212

dalujachakshu@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/chakshudaluja/ https://chaksd.github.io/ChakshuDalujaPortfolio/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Colour Theory

Heuristic Evaluation

Interviews

Information Architecture

Interactive design

Journey Maps

Responsive Design

Research and Analysis

Storyboard

Surveys

Persona Creation

Prototyping

User Flows

Usability Testing

Wireframing

Figma

Adobe XD

Canva

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

GitHub

JQuery

Visual Studio Code

Soft Skills

Analytic Intelligence

Emotional Intelligence

Problem Solving

Effective Communication

Growth Mindset

Result Oriented

EDUCATION

UI/UX Boot Camp

2022 | Monash University

Agent Rep & Owners Corporation Management

2015 | REIV

Bachelor of Journalism

2006 | La Trobe University

Achievement

Golden Key awarded on merit basis | La Trobe University